♪♪
Sea Spray... when you
have to smell your very best.
Cut.
Let's take five, people.
Oh, for God's sake,
the line is "Sea Spray...
"for when you have
to feel your very best."
"Feel", not "smell".
Can't she read?
It's a deodorant commercial.
She got confused.
Oh, I never should have
let you talk me into hiring her.
My mistake.
Grace, the girl is on
the cover of Vogue.
Tell her if she doesn't
get it right on the next take,
she can go back on
the cover of Vogue.
Where's Peter Angelli?
I've got an appointment
downtown in 20 minutes.
Will you be home for dinner?
Richard, I told you this morning,
I've got a board meeting tonight.
- Do you want me there?
- It's business, Richard.
I just thought you
might want me there.
It's business, Richard.
Peter! Over here.
Don't wait up for
me. I'll be home late.
- Problems with the boy wonder?
- Hmm.
You should've let
me handle this, Grace.
Peter, you were with my dad
when he started this business,
so I'm not going to
play games with you.
Hi, Peter.
Two years ago, you were our
busiest commercial director.
But, you know,
economics are changing.
The advertisers, they're not
buying as many new campaigns,
and when they do buy one,
they want to make sure that
what they're buying looks new.
Your commercials look old.
Don't sugarcoat it, Grace.
Is this your way of saying
you want me to run a desk?
No, no desk.
I'm sorry, Peter, but I'm
taking you off of salary,
effective the first
of next month.
Now, Grace, look,
please... The way things are,
if you fire me now, at my age, I
won't be able to get a job again.
I am really very sorry.
Damn it!
Peter, I would like to get
into my car now, please.
You wouldn't have a car
if it hadn't been for me!
I helped your father
build this company!
I know, but Dad's gone,
and I make the decisions
for Harker Productions now.
If you ask me, the
wrong Harker is dead.
You're fired!
It's over!
Can't you do anything, Richard?
It's her company.
I'm sorry, Peter.
Yeah.
Grace!
- My God. I know what you think.
- Really?
Get her out of the
house, Richard, now.
I'll see you in the den.
Grace.
I know I hurt you.
I made a mistake. It
was a terrible mistake.
I made a mistake expecting
anything more from you.
What do you mean?
She wasn't the first,
she won't be the last.
Grace, sweetheart...
they don't mean anything
to me. You know that.
Come on, I love you.
Oh, stop it.
Love never had anything
to do with our arrangement.
You married me because you wanted
a ready-made life on the fast track.
I married you for exactly the
same reason you slept with that girl.
Let's not delude ourselves.
How can you say that?
It's the truth, and
I'm tired of lies.
Have a drink, Richard.
You can sleep in
the guest bedroom.
Oh, Grace, please.
I'll call my lawyer on
Monday. I want a divorce.
Meet me in the
studio in ten minutes.
I don't care, just
meet me there!
Do you think she'll
change her mind?
Grace Harker Maitland
Grace wants a divorce,
Grace gets a divorce.
End of discussion.
So, you get yourself
a good lawyer.
Kevin, I signed a
prenuptial agreement.
How bad?
Bad.
Richard...
Look, I don't know what to say.
Oh.
Oh, this is your problem, too.
Ohh.
You think she's going to keep my
big brother on the company payroll
after I'm gone?
If this happens, we are
both on the street, buddy boy,
just like Angelli.
And I put up with too much for
too long to end up with nothing.
Well, what are you going to do?
I don't know.
I guess I will try
to talk to her again.
Hey, Louie, is my
brother here yet?
He got in a few minutes
ago, Mr. Maitland.
- Very good.
- See you later.
- What did you do?
- Come on!
What did you do?
Uh, how much
is it going to cost?
When you don't paint a
place, the paint starts to peel,
the wood gets exposed.
The next thing you
know, it starts to rot.
No good, Mr. Matlock.
No damn good.
How much?
Ron...
if I had any idea I was dealing
with the Michelangelo of Atlanta,
I never would have
wasted your time or mine.
Have a nice day.
I can do a real
nice job for you.
Have a nice day.
- It's highway robbery.
- What?
The last time I had
this house painted,
it was under $200...
Scraping and everything.
The last time you
painted this house,
Richard Nixon was
running for Vice President.
Ben, I just got a call
from an old family friend.
He's being brought in for
questioning about a murder,
and he needs a lawyer.
- No, not me.
- Oh, Ben.
Every time I try to get a
little work done on the house,
another case gets in the way.
Now, I've got to draw the
line somewhere, Michelle.
I'm going to get this old house
painted if I have to do it myself.
Ben, he's a family friend.
I can't turn him away.
Well, hell, you're a
lawyer. Take it yourself.
Well, yeah, I am a lawyer.
Yeah, the best in Atlanta.
Yeah? Except for you.
- I'm a house painter.
- Ha ha!
OK, I'll do it.
I'd better get on downtown.
If you want to talk to
somebody, I'll be right here...
or up there.
Mr. Angelli, I understand you had
an argument with Grace Maitland
on the film set
yesterday afternoon.
Don't answer that.
And didn't you say to her,
"The wrong Harker is dead"?
I was angry. She said
she was going to fire me.
Peter, if you want
me to represent you,
you're going to
have to do what I say.
I'm sounding guilty
here, and I'm not.
I would like to discuss this.
Do you still have a job
now that she's dead?
Don't answer that!
Richard Maitland
and his secretary
spoke with Mrs.
Maitland at 7:40 A.M.
She was found by the maid at
8:50, an hour and ten minutes later.
Somebody pushed
her down the stairs.
Mr. Angelli, where were you
between 7:40 and 8:50 this morning?
My client was at
home asleep, alone.
When was the last time you
were in the Maitland house?
Christmas.
- And you haven't been back since?
- No.
- No?
Well, then, tell me...
How did these get
on the staircase?
I own four or five
pair of those glasses.
How am I supposed to
know how they got there?
I think you do know.
Counselor, I'm afraid I'm going to
have to charge your client with murder.
Here's to life
insurance, big brother.
$2 million.
May not be worth as
much as her estate,
but at least the insurance
money is all mine.
Ours.
Well, that's what I meant. Ours.
Get rid of these.
Who is it?
Some fat guy. I
never saw him before.
Hi there.
You got some lawn out there.
That's tremendous.
You don't mow it
yourself, do you?
No, of course not.
Of course not. Do you
know what kind of blisters
you'd get on your
hands if you did that?
Excuse me, who are you?
I'm Max Sugarman, North
American Mutual Life Insurance.
May I come in?
What a lawn.
Wow!
Excuse me?
Look at this house.
I thought the lawn was big.
- Mr. Sugarman...
- Max, please.
Oh, you have a gift shop.
I've got to bring
something back.
Hi there.
Mr. Sugarman, I
don't need insurance.
I don't sell insurance.
You'd be surprised how many
people make that mistake.
I think it's the outfit.
I've got to get a new outfit.
Mr. Sugarman, my wife just
died, so if you don't mind...
I am so sorry about your wife.
Actually, that's why
I'm here. I'm an adjuster.
An adjuster?
North American Mutual carried
a $2 million policy on your wife,
and you're listed as
the sole beneficiary.
Yeah, that's right.
Grace wanted it that way.
Well, under those
circumstances... $2 million...
We have to investigate.
Investigate?
Strictly routine.
Do you have a pen?
A pen? Yes, I think I do.
Uh, do I have to sign something?
No, I do.
Thank you.
This will take a second.
Sign, sign, sign.
Your wife...
Did she have any enemies?
No.
What about Peter?
I don't think so.
Well, don't worry.
I've taken enough of your time.
Sorry to bother you.
This is some house.
- Mr. Sugarman?
- Yes?
My pen?
Pen. Right.
I've got to get one
of these on a chain.
Then again, I'd
probably lose the chain.
We'll keep in touch.
I don't understand.
Is there a problem?
I thought the police charged
Peter Angelli with Grace's murder?
Yeah, well, that's
easy for them to say.
It's not their money.
Peter's innocent, Ben.
I'm sure of it.
And the evidence against
him is all circumstantial.
Somebody must have
planted those sunglasses.
What do you think?
If I buy 20 gallons, I
can get this for half price.
That's an awful color.
You think so?
You don't want a
goldfish orange house.
Well, I thought I'd
try something new.
No, stick with green and white.
But they won't give me a
discount on green and white.
Oh, that must be Conrad.
Do you want some help?
I'd rather get a little
further into the case?
You're not really going to paint
this place yourself, are you?
At the prices these painters
charge, I'm seriously considering it.
Mr. Matlock.
Max Sugarman... North
American Mutual Insurance.
Thanks, I don't need any.
No, no, no. I understand
you represent Peter Angelli.
May I come in? Thank you.
Wow, what a nice house.
Very traditional.
Well aged. I like it.
If you don't mind me saying so,
the outside could use a little paint.
Uh, Mr. Sugarman?
Are you connected with the
Peter Angelli murder case?
North American Mutual Insurance
held a policy on the victim.
I don't know if you guys need help,
but we're working on the same case.
Let's work together.
This is Michelle
Thomas, my associate.
She's in charge.
I have a very
important appointment.
The paint store closes at 5:00.
- Green and white?
- Green and white.
OK. Well, Mr. Sugarman.
Mr. Matlock?
I'd stick with the
green and white.
- Mr. Sugarman...
- Max, please.
Michelle.
Hello.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
$2 million... That's
some motive for murder.
Have you talked to the husband?
This afternoon.
Maitland was there
with his brother.
- He didn't say too much but...
- But?
I think they were
drinking champagne,
and they didn't want
me to know about it.
People don't usually drink
champagne to drown their sorrows.
That's right. They
use it for celebrations...
New Year's, weddings,
your Uncle Morty's
store burning down.
It's an insurance joke.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, I think pooling our
resources is a fine idea.
Great. I have the home office
doing background research
on Maitland, Harker
Productions, everything.
If you have anything,
a lead... Anything...
My friend Christy's a model.
I think she's worked
for Harker Productions.
Maybe she knows something
about Richard Maitland.
I was going to call her myself,
but I'm due at
Peter's trial hearing.
Great. That's
wonderful. I'll call her.
Women love talking to me.
I think it's my
animal magnetism.
Probably.
- Hi.
- Hello. Yes, sir?
- Where are you going?
- Anywhere.
You want a little job of work?
Yeah, I'd take one.
- Do you know how to paint?
- A little bit.
- Hop in.
- All right.
Are you hungry?
Well, I'll tell you... You put
something in front of me,
turn your head and
turn back real quick,
and if it ain't
gone, I ain't hungry.
You like hot dogs?
How about fried chicken?
I like a man that
speaks his mind.
You ain't going to
rob me, are you?
No, I gave that
up a long time ago.
Do I look like I
need life insurance?
No, you don't.
A friend of a friend of mine tells me
that you used to date Richard Maitland.
Ha! The worst year of my life.
- Would you?
- Hmm, yeah.
The buckle... Would
you buckle it, please?
- Just...
- Yeah, all right.
Thank you.
Why do you want to
know about Richard?
Someone killed his wife.
Oh! Oh, my God.
And you suspect Richard?
Richard may be scum,
but killing Grace was
the last thing he'd do.
Why is that?
She was his
ticket to first class.
She made him sign a
prenuptial agreement.
And what was in this agreement?
He used to cry
about it all the time.
If he ever left her or she
ever left him, he got zip.
Would you?
Would I what?
- Zip me up.
- Oh, yeah. Sure.
But isn't that a good enough
reason for him to kill her?
For her money?
Grace inherited from her father.
When she dies, it goes
to her younger brother.
Richard had nothing
to gain from her death.
Yeah, just $2 million.
Sorry?
I'm just speaking to myself.
Is it possible that if a
friend of a friend of mine
knows that you had
an affair with Richard,
then his wife knew?
Yeah, that's why it ended.
Grace would shake the leash,
and good dog Richard came to heel.
Are you going to wear that?
Me? No, no.
Much better on you.
Very nice.
See you around.
And cut.
Very nice.
Very nice, very nice.
Can we all listen
up for a minute here?
- Hi.
It's amazing, that
guy actually gets paid
to sit there, kissing that girl.
Tough job.
I thought insurance
was glamorous.
Mr. Sugarman, who's
your lovely friend?
Michelle Thomas. I'm
defending Peter Angelli.
You're an attorney?
What a waste.
We know you're
busy, Mr. Maitland.
- We just have one or two questions.
- What?
Do you know a woman
named Lisa Loomis?
I suppose Lisa told
you about our affair?
She mentioned it.
She also mentioned
your wife found out.
Grace found out
because I told her.
Lisa was a foolish
mistake, and Grace knew it.
It took some time, but we put
our marriage back together...
Better than it was before.
Really?
You may find this difficult
to believe, Miss Thomas,
but my wife and I loved
and trusted each other.
Well, if she loved and
trusted you, Mr. Maitland,
why did she make you
sign a prenuptial agreement
that left you nothing in
the event of a divorce?
You think I killed her?
No, no. Of course not.
- Maybe a little.
- Well, I didn't.
In fact, I was making a
video test at the time she died.
Can we see this...
Make an appointment with my
secretary and you can see it tomorrow.
After you do, I expect your
company to pay my claim.
And if they don't,
I'll see you in court.
♪ Gonna have a
little talk with Jesus ♪
♪ When I get home tonight ♪
♪ Gonna tell him all
about my troubles ♪
♪ And I know he'll
make them right ♪
♪ Then I'll ask
him to forgive me ♪
♪ For the things that
I've done wrong ♪
♪ Gonna have a
little talk with Jesus ♪
♪ When I get home tonight ♪
Oh, that's wonderful.
Um, Billy, you're...
You're not making
a lot of progress.
Yeah, well, it is slow,
but it's coming along.
Uh, I'm trying not to scrape off
the house with all that old paint.
Oh, yeah, well...
why don't you come
down and have a peanut
and we'll talk about it?
Don't mind if I do.
Uh, I thought you said
you knew how to paint?
No, I said I'd done
some painting...
Barns and outhouses
and stuff like that.
Oh, barns and outhouses
Yeah.
Where did you get that guitar?
Well, I bought this off
a fellow who was, uh...
Let's say, in a hurry to catch a
train, and I gave him a dollar for it.
A dollar?
Yeah, well, he was in a
hurry, and a dollar's all I had.
A dollar?
Yeah. It didn't
look like much then,
but I tightened
up the loose joints
and I scraped all the cracked
finish and garbage off of it,
and then I sanded it,
just like I've been doing
to that window up there.
Well, Billy, a house
is not like a guitar.
You just kind of scrape
it and then paint it.
Yeah.
Then I refinished it.
Took more than five
months, off and on...
You know, when I'd stay
in a place long enough.
But now it sounds
just like an organ.
Well, when you can...
It won't sound like an organ,
but, with any kind of luck,
it might look like a house.
♪ I'm the life of the party ♪
♪ I'm everybody's friend ♪
♪ The center of attention ♪
♪ That's how it's always been ♪
♪ They love to see me coming ♪
♪ And they hate to see me go ♪
♪ But it's just a
game I'm playing ♪
♪ And I'll never let them know ♪
♪ And I can almost
hear your laughter ♪
♪ When I turn out the light ♪
♪ And the life of the party ♪
♪ Dies a little every night ♪
♪ Yeah, the life of the party ♪
Ooh, I'll take two of these.
And two of these.
And, oh, these look
good. I'll take two of these.
- Like anything?
- No.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
Max says that you think Richard
Maitland may have killed his wife.
He was having an affair. If she
found out and wanted a divorce,
he would have been
left without a dime.
Oh.
So, he set up your client
to try to get $2 million
of my company's money.
That's a lot of donuts.
The trouble is, Richard
Maitland claims he has an alibi
on videotape at his studio.
Maybe Conrad ought to go
over there and look around.
Maybe he'll get a lead.
Maitland said he'd show
us the tape this morning,
but you and I have a pretrial
hearing in five minutes.
Max, could you...
I'm on my way.
There you go.
Enjoy them.
Don't look at me. I
don't eat that stuff.
Left you holding the
bill, huh, Mr. Matlock?
How is the focus?
Looking good.
We do video tests on every
commercial we produce.
We need to see how the
product looks on screen,
whether the set needs any
special lighting or presentation.
Well, so, this is
the test you made
the morning your
wife was killed?
Kevin was behind the
camera. I handled the product.
I thought your
brother was in sales.
How come he was
working the camera?
We're a very small company.
Everybody does double
duty on all sides of the camera.
Well, they're talking
about regional saturation...
How do you do that?
Very well.
I remember we left a
TV on during the test.
See the monitor
in the background?
The Channel 9
morning show was on.
Now, if you watch carefully,
you can see the time
whenever they do the news.
7:45.
Five minutes after my
secretary and I called Grace.
Now, watch.
I saw War and Peace this
way. It took me eight minutes.
Oh, 9:00.
Ten minutes after
Grace was found dead.
You can run the tape back
and forth, Mr. Sugarman.
There isn't a cut
longer than five minutes.
Really?
You can check it
against the morning show.
I was there from
7:45 until 9:00.
Satisfied?
What can I say?
That's some alibi.
You can say that you're
going to pay my claim.
Oh, hey. Oh.
- Excuse me.
- Who the hell are you?
Johnson, Mr. Maitland. I
came to work on your machines.
- Well, then work on it.
- OK.
Last try... When
do I get my money?
Yeah, well, can I get
a copy of that tape?
I've stood for this long
enough, Sugarman.
I'll see you in court. Out.
Out?
- Out.
You don't validate, do you?
- What's he looking for?
- It's just routine. Relax.
You said there was
going to be no problem.
Something's wrong.
Something's not right.
Will you just relax?!
What if they don't give us the
money? What are we going to do?
Sugarman's seen the tape.
They don't have a choice.
They'll have to pay off.
My God, Richard,
what's happening to us?
- We should never have done it.
- We've done it.
I wish you'd just shut...
All right, now, zoom in.
- OK, I'm in.
- Now crank it up to...
Maybe we should watch
the tape one more time.
Max, we've seen
it six times already.
Bear with me. Have
a little patience.
And in the second place,
the longest cut I saw
was only four minutes.
Not enough time to go home.
Right. Richard Maitland
was there from 7:45 to 9:00,
just like he said.
Which means he didn't kill her.
And if Kevin was
running the camera...
He didn't kill her, either. But
that doesn't make any sense.
You heard them.
He was coming apart.
In another minute,
he would have
admitted the whole thing.
Stop the tape.
Can you blow that up?
Sure.
9:30.
Maitland's watch says 9:30.
Grace Maitland was
killed before 9:00.
They must have
taped the morning show
and played it back
after she was dead.
They killed her.
Hey, Billy?
Yeah?
You've been painting on that
same window for two days.
Two days you've
been painting on it,
and you got more paint on the
floor than you did on the window.
I guess I'm not cut
out for this kind of work.
Yeah, I guess not.
Well, come on in. I'll fix
us something for lunch.
Sorry I couldn't
do a little better.
Well, I'm just going to
have to hire a real painter.
That's what I should
have done to start with.
They're sky-high.
You can't keep your hands
off that thing, can you?
Well, it's with
me day and night.
It's about the
only friend I've got.
Sometimes me and this guitar
make enough money out on the street
that we have enough food to eat
and a place to stay
for two or three days.
- Hmm.
- Ha ha!
♪ Come sit by my side ♪
♪ Little darling ♪
♪ Come lay your cool hand ♪
♪ On my brow ♪
♪ And promise me ♪
♪ That you will never ♪
♪ Be nobody's darling ♪
♪ But mine ♪
♪ Nobody's darling ♪
♪ But mine, love ♪
♪ Be honest ♪
♪ And faithful and kind ♪
♪ And promise me ♪
♪ That you will never ♪
♪ Be nobody's darling ♪
♪ But mine ♪
♪ You're as sweet as ♪
♪ The flowers in springtime ♪
♪ You're as pure as the dew ♪
♪ From the rose ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ Somebody's darling ♪
♪ Than a poor boy ♪
♪ That nobody knows ♪
♪ Nobody's darling ♪
♪ But mine, love ♪
♪ Be honest ♪
♪ Be faithful and kind ♪
♪ And promise me ♪
♪ That you will never ♪
♪ Be nobody's darling ♪
♪ But mine ♪
I didn't know you
played the ukulele?
Oh, yeah.
I've been wanting to pick a piece
with you ever since I heard you play.
- All right.
- That was fun.
You know, Billy,
you're never going
to make a living
running around the
country doing odd jobs.
You're no good at it.
I've got to do something.
Well, you ought to try
something that you're good at.
Like what?
Like picking and singing.
- You think so?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you sing
the old-timey way,
not that... not that
country rock 'n' roll stuff.
And you've got that
twang to your voice.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we ought to
get you a cowboy outfit.
I mean, you can't tell.
You sing good, and
you're fairly good looking.
You never know, you might
have some kind of future.
- Where's Richard? Mr. Maitland?
- He left.
Something's wrong.
I got a message.
- I was supposed to pick him up.
- He left.
- Where did he go?
- He was in a hurry.
I think he said the studio.
I just came from there.
What are they doing?
Putting the
furniture in storage.
Who told them to
do that? The estate?
No, Mr. Maitland.
Look, I'm sorry, I don't
know what's going on.
But if you find Mr. Maitland,
you ask him, okay?
- Is my brother here?
- He just left.
- Do you know where he went?
- No.
Let me check with the secretary.
Hi, Peggy. Louis, at the gate.
How are you doing?
Mr. Maitland's brother is here,
trying to find out where he went.
Yeah, he just left. OK.
Really? OK, great. Thanks.
Peggy says she heard
him call Miss Loomis.
He said something
about coming right over.
He's seeing Lisa again?
She says everybody's looking
for Mr. Maitland this morning.
Who else?
She mentioned an
insurance man and a cop.
Oh, my God.
I'm coming.
- Where's Richard?
- He isn't here.
Richard!
Look, Kevin, I just
told you... Kevin...
He called you. He said
he was coming here.
You just missed him. He left for
the airport about 15 minutes ago.
I don't understand.
Yeah, he asked
me to go with him.
I told him, "Not on your life."
He's leaving the country.
He mentioned Paris.
I got the feeling he plans
to be gone a long time.
Anyway, do you mind? I was
just about to take a shower.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I thought
he was here.
Yoo-hoo? Kevin?
Hi, Kevin.
Remember me?
Max Sugarman, North
American Mutual Insurance.
I know, you're probably saying to
yourself, "I'm young, I'm healthy.
"I eat right. I don't
need insurance."
That's where you're wrong.
Everybody needs insurance.
Your brother left town,
left you here all alone
to talk to the police.
You need a lot of
insurance, Mr. Maitland.
And Max Sugarman, North
American Mutual Insurance,
is here to help you.
Look, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Richard is not going to leave me
to take the blame for everything.
No way.
Does your client
understand his rights?
I told him he doesn't have
to answer any questions...
And I am making a statement.
This wasn't my idea.
- Whose idea was it?
- It was Richard's.
Richard knew Grace
was going to divorce him?
Oh, yeah.
And if she did,
he'd wind up broke.
I mean, we both would.
So, you decided to kill her?
No, no. That was Richard's idea.
How did you do it?
Richard came to work that morning
and called Grace from his office.
We set up a cassette machine
to record Atlanta This Morning.
And... then I met him
out back, in my car.
We drove to the house...
and Richard killed her.
We came back to the studio.
We shot the test with the
cassette playing in the background.
I mean, that way it looked as if
neither one of us had ever left.
Richard said it would
be the perfect alibi.
We'll get this typed up.
Are you sure you want
to sign it, Mr. Maitland?
Do you have a pen?
Put Mr. Maitland in my office.
Michelle.
Max. How did it go?
Perfect.
You... Sugarman!
I want to know what's going on.
Your people had me down
in your office all morning
waiting for my check.
Really? All morning?
Did you get paid?
No.
And then these two clowns showed
up and dragged me down here.
If you had anything to
do with this, Sugarman,
I swear I'll have you
charged with harassment.
Not before we charge you
with murder, Mr. Maitland.
They told...
They told me you
left the country.
Oh, no, Richard
didn't leave the country.
Did you, Richard?
Well, I understand I owe
you a lot, Mr. Sugarman.
Please, Max.
Max arranged everything...
The moving van,
getting the maid's cooperation,
the people at the studio,
and Lisa Loomis.
She was the kicker, huh?
Nice girl.
I think she liked me.
So, Mr. Angelli, what now?
You know what they
say... In my business,
there's no such
thing as bad publicity.
Believe it or not, I am getting
offers to direct from all over...
Commercials, music videos...
Did I hear somebody say
something about music and videos?
Mr. Angelli, I'd like you
to meet a friend of mine.
He's a slow painter
but a fine singer.
With all your connections with
commercials and the music world,
maybe you can help the boy
out. I think he's got possibilities.
♪ I'm going to that road ♪
♪ Feeling bad ♪
♪ I'm going down that road ♪
♪ Feeling bad, Lord, Lord ♪
♪ And I ain't gonna be treated ♪
♪ This way ♪
♪ Well, I'm down in the jail ♪
♪ On my knees ♪
♪ Down in the jail ♪
♪ I'm down in the jail ♪
♪ On my knees, Lord, Lord ♪
♪ And I ain't gonna be treated ♪
♪ This way ♪
♪ They're feeding
me on cornbread ♪
♪ And peas ♪
♪ They're feeding
me on cornbread ♪
♪ And peas, yes, yes ♪
♪ They're feeding
me on cornbread ♪
♪ And peas, Lord, Lord ♪
♪ And I ain't gonna be treated ♪
♪ This way ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net